<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on JGB</title>
    <link>http://galeanobra.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on JGB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://galeanobra.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>El efecto de la multiconectividad en el problema del apagado selectivo de redes 5G ultradensas</title>
      <link>http://galeanobra.github.io/publications/quinones2021efecto/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://galeanobra.github.io/publications/quinones2021efecto/</guid>
      <description>In XIX Conferencia de la Asociación Española para la Inteligencia Artificial El despliegue masivo de estaciones base es uno de los pilares básicos para que las nuevas generaciones de redes móviles satisfagan las elevadas demandas de muchas aplicaciones actuales. Esta densificación conlleva, no obstante, un elevado consumo energético que ha de ser minimizado para garantizar la sostenibilidad del sistema en un claro contexto de reducción del impacto ambiental. Se trata, por tanto, de un problema de optimización multiobjetivo en el que no sólo se tienen en cuenta criterios de eficiencia energética, si no también de calidad del servicio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detection and Mitigation of DoS and DDoS Attacks in IoT-Based Stateful SDN: An Experimental Approach</title>
      <link>http://galeanobra.github.io/publications/galeano2020detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://galeanobra.github.io/publications/galeano2020detection/</guid>
      <description>The expected advent of the Internet of Things (IoT) has triggered a large demand of embedded devices, which envisions the autonomous interaction of sensors and actuators while offering all sort of smart services. However, these IoT devices are limited in computation, storage, and network capacity, which makes them easy to hack and compromise. To achieve secure development of IoT, it is necessary to engineer scalable security solutions optimized for the IoT ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detection and mitigation of DoS attacks in SDN. An experimental approach</title>
      <link>http://galeanobra.github.io/publications/galeano2019detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://galeanobra.github.io/publications/galeano2019detection/</guid>
      <description>In 2019 Sixth International Conference on Internet of Things: Systems, Management and Security (IOTSMS) The expected advent of the Internet of Things (IoT) has triggered a large demand of embedded devices, which envisions the autonomous interaction of these sensors and actuators while offering all sort of smart services. However, these IoT devices are limited in compute, storage, and network capacity which makes them easy to hack and compromise. To achieve a safe development of IoT, it is necessary to develop scalable security solutions optimized for the IoT ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
